<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Azure AD on Microsoft 365 Platform Community Blog</title><link>https://pnp.github.io/blog/tags/azure-ad/</link><description>Recent content in Azure AD on Microsoft 365 Platform Community Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:17:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pnp.github.io/blog/tags/azure-ad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PnP PowerShell v1.10</title><link>https://pnp.github.io/blog/pnp-powershell/pnp-powershell-v1-10/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 12:17:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://pnp.github.io/blog/pnp-powershell/pnp-powershell-v1-10/</guid><description>PnP PowerShell is a cross-platform PowerShell Module providing over 600 cmdlets that work with Microsoft 365 environments and more specifically SharePoint Online, Microsoft Teams, Microsoft Planner and Power Automate.</description></item><item><title>CLI for Microsoft 365 v4.4</title><link>https://pnp.github.io/blog/cli-for-microsoft-365/cli-for-microsoft-365-v4-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 12:17:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://pnp.github.io/blog/cli-for-microsoft-365/cli-for-microsoft-365-v4-4/</guid><description>CLI for Microsoft 365 is a cross-platform CLI that allows you to manage various configuration settings of Microsoft 365 and SharePoint Framework projects no matter which operating system or shell you use</description></item><item><title>Looking at things in profile</title><link>https://pnp.github.io/blog/post/looking-at-things-in-profile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 08:40:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://pnp.github.io/blog/post/looking-at-things-in-profile/</guid><description>User Profiles are an increasingly important part of a modern organisation While they have always been important as a (often underused) tool for finding staff and searching for people with certain skills, the changes in work practice wrought by the COVID-19 pandemic now mean that staff spend less time together physically, so have less opportunity to know their colleagues and create the social and personal links that team-building and socialisation rely on.</description></item><item><title>Change your own profile picture as a Guest in Microsoft Teams</title><link>https://pnp.github.io/blog/post/change-your-own-profile-picture-as-a-guest-in-microsoft-teams/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 01:37:00 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://pnp.github.io/blog/post/change-your-own-profile-picture-as-a-guest-in-microsoft-teams/</guid><description>I love Microsoft Teams and I also love controlling my online appearance, but sadly both aren&amp;rsquo;t big friends when you are a Guest in another tenant.</description></item></channel></rss>